[Kaspar]: You are listening to clap to clap part three.
[Kaspar]: on Collaboradio.org as a part of Freie Radio's Berlin Brandenburg.
[Kaspar]: Streaming on www.wr-bb.org and Collaboradio.org.
[Kaspar]: Transmitting on DAB Plus channel 7D for Berlin and channel 12D for Brandenburg.
[Kaspar]: This is a radio show made by Kaspar König and I do a lot of interviews and sound recordings from Colab, Technobiological Futures, a project by the artist and biohacking labs hosted on Hectoria.
[Kaspar]: www.hackteria.org.
[Kaspar]: Listeners are invited into a global network of makers exploring the collective motivation behind the work and the unique context of this collaborative lab culture.
[Kaspar]: The show is edited and produced between Zurich and the Yemen town so expect a few holes here and there both in the sound and the narrative.
[Kaspar]: Alongside uncovering these collaborations, the episode dips into music and sound art made in the Divo spirit.
[Kaspar]: Do it with others.
[Kaspar]: Today we will highlight the yearly homemade event which took place in the last week of July of this year in Skiertalen, St.
[Kaspar]: Gallen in Switzerland.
[Kaspar]: And we will have a listen to some of the interviews, field recordings and snippets from concerts.
[Kaspar]: Also I want to just point out that there's a lot of friends out there in this network that will gather again from 7 to 11 of September in the circuit control in Dresden.
[Kaspar]: So if you're there around then you will just deep dive into that D-Wall spirit immediately.
[Kaspar]: Now we're gonna listen to a first snippet.
[Participant]: things you would normally see.
[Participant]: You see, so we cannot be free.
[Participant]: Might be, might be.
[Participant]: We cannot really talk like because now this is going somewhere.
[Participant]: It's not recording, it's only recording if it's bright.
[Participant]: I don't know if I understand what he was saying.
[Participant]: So now it's not too much.
[Participant]: Like we cannot really talk about some things that they are controversial.
[Participant]: Like a compromise.
[Participant]: Our own opinions or what you say.
[Participant]: I don't know if I understand.
[Participant]: I mean, when you work in the company, normally the things which are written, they are relevant for lawyers.
[Participant]: So anything which is written, which is documented in a company, it somehow you can sue it with lawyers.
[Participant]: Normally before when you said something in a meeting I mean it was just forgotten there was no documentation it could not be sued but today you have to be very careful in saying anything in any meeting because afterwards it's documented in the company and when other company comes and just looks into the logs then it's very clear what was happening very precisely.
[Participant]: What does it have to do with AI?
[Participant]: that the language and the voice recognition of the AI is possible in this quality let's say since three years before it was not possible to log during a meeting every I mean afterwards and that's the point because then you have big data files and these data files you can just
[Participant]: You can just do a search function with your computer on the data files.
[Participant]: You can you can find in this data files any word or any sentence you said and you couldn't do that before.
[Participant]: And that's the big difference since voice recognition with AI is in this meeting.
[Participant]: So why are you laughing now?
[Marc Dusseiller]: I'd farted.
[Participant]: Like human being.
[Participant]: Like the name of the workshop, Scheiss, right?
[Participant]: Everyone farts.
[Participant]: Yeah, yeah.
[Participant]: Taking to the theme.
[Participant]: What's the name of the company?
[Participant]: The name of the workshop is S-C-H-A-I-S-S, which means Scheiss.
[Participant]: And you understand German, so Scheiss as a shit AI.
[Participant]: So this is a wordplay.
[Kaspar]: Thank you.
[Participant]: And because he farted now and it's smelling, he was just laughing.
[Music]: Hmm.
[Kaspar]: I'm making radio for Collabor Radio and that's a Berlin free radio.
[Kaspar]: And I was wondering if I could just describe what you are doing because you are doing something very special.
[Pije]: And because you're doing Berlin radio it has to be in English because that's what Berlin is today.
[Kaspar]: And I think I reach for people.
[Pije]: So that's why I do this.
[Kaspar]: So the English version is a wrap top.
[Pije]: A wrap top.
[Pije]: Yeah, but the German version is a clip top.
[Pije]: A clip top.
[Kaspar]: So what do you do then?
[Kaspar]: Can you describe what you're doing?
[Pije]: I clip the clip fully on the laptop.
[Kaspar]: So you have a wrap up.
[Pije]: Yes, it's deeply philosophical.
[Pije]: I will not submit to the design choices of the capitalist system.
[Pije]: Look, we all know that the worst computers you can get are Macs.
[Pije]: They are also very beautiful.
[Pije]: So what I try is I have a real machine.
[Pije]: It's 15 years old, which still makes it better than a current day Apple machine, of course, because it's a computer, not an Apple machine.
[Pije]: But I try to make it more beautiful.
[Kaspar]: Absolutely.
[Gandalf]: I'm Gandalf.
[Gandalf]: I've been a regular participant at Homemade for decades, almost.
[Gandalf]: Homemade being the annual summer camp of the Swiss mechatronic art society.
[Gandalf]: where people are tinkering with electronics or mechanical devices.
[Gandalf]: One of the things I'm featuring is a sticker printing service called Sticker Central, where people can print stickers on small brother QL label printers.
[Gandalf]: I've also been doing quite a lot of bruschographie, which is basically an aquarelle painting robot.
[Gandalf]: That takes away the pain of manually creating art.
[Gandalf]: You just upload or you generate your design, you upload it to the machine and it will paint it for you.
[Valentina]: I'm Valentina, I'm also a participant, this is my seventh home mate.
[Valentina]: I appreciate the very self-organization and the democracy between us and we are very different and there is a lot of diversity.
[Valentina]: but we are together and we are working together, we are eating together, speaking together.
[Valentina]: I, for example, perform data art.
[Valentina]: I can collaborate, also meet other scientists, they could give me some data and I can make sculpture 3D and print it and to make beautiful visuals based on code and data.
[Valentina]: In normal artistic life, we are not artists.
[Valentina]: We are normal jobs.
[Valentina]: We have some normal jobs and normal life.
[Valentina]: But this is a special context to be self and to express yourself and to be free.
[Valentina]: To be free, do it yourself, do it with others and to have fun one week.
[Valentina]: Collaboration, trans-disciplinarity, across disciplines.
[Valentina]: We are going across disciplines.
[Valentina]: This is something in between, between social and natural science, between coding and creating.
[Kaspar]: Thank you so much.
[Valentina]: Yeah, welcome, welcome.
[Kaspar]: I'm sorry.
[Cows]: Yeah, that's what you have to know.
[Kaspar]: So in the middle of Gierlen homemade festival 2026 I meet up with an artist that I think is marvelous in doing object theater I would call it with beautiful sounds of course.
[Kaspar]: But I will leave the introduction and the reason why he is also a homemade to him to tell us as listeners and in the background the cows will listen as well along the story.
[Flo]: Hello, my name is Flo Kaufmann and my project is called Bricolage Universal, which means in French.
[Flo]: There's no expression in English or German that can describe what Bricolage means, but it's like improvising, it's taking things that you find that's abuse of stuff,
[Flo]: like all this childish approach to build stuff.
[Kaspar]: And you do that since?
[Flo]: I do that since I would say 93 something like this.
[Flo]: I did it already before but before it was not really called art and then somehow I got I was falling into this art scene.
[Flo]: I have I did already like as a kid doing strange pretty collage with sounds with electronic like Philips electronic custom and
[Flo]: but then one day someone came and said this is basically art what you're doing and they were falling into it with festivals and events and since then yeah I tried to have fun in this wonderful community and you're based in?
[Flo]: I'm based in Solatron that's between Basel and Bern, Lausanne, Zurich everything is one hour away so quite central in Switzerland yeah
[Kaspar]: And if you see homemade as a collaborative laboratory, would you agree on that?
[Kaspar]: Or would you see there?
[Flo]: Totally.
[Flo]: I mean, homemade is the co-op event.
[Flo]: It's so many people showing their work, share their work, doing workshops.
[Kaspar]: You get just inspired by just looking at what people
[Flo]: working on or presenting so and it's so like without I mean there's basically no structure and it somehow works.
[Flo]: A week full of crazy people and for me it's always a highlight for sure to get charged batteries and to go it's it's hard to really work focused on on staff but sometimes you really have this also this really well prepared
[Flo]: workshops and then you have wonderful concerts out of nothing and yeah this is this is co-op yeah yeah and next to your family did you also bring a project or something you presented earlier
[Flo]: I came with a small little workshop of basically two.
[Flo]: I showed a little bit how I process black and white in a very most simple and primitive way without the dark room, something I figured out for myself and I thought it's maybe interesting for other people, especially in this digital world.
[Flo]: And so I shared this and then I have some kind of an arpeggiator kit that somehow felt a little bit under.
[Flo]: I wanted especially to have all this brain work of people to collaborate with in software reflection how to do it and this somehow there were so many
[Flo]: other things to so much distraction so this i made the hardware i made already last year and this year i made a first software version and at least i can have some prepared kits to to give away you know in these little plastic bags like everyone else i have at least now a new giveaway back so yeah super super and can you describe the the secret behind this black and white
[Flo]: Well, there's no secret.
[Flo]: There's just a way I'm doing it.
[Flo]: It starts with that I don't have a dark room.
[Flo]: I just have this little bag where you go with your hands inside and do everything in darkness.
[Flo]: and then you load the film and then it's about which chemistry I use.
[Flo]: I use a very old highly diluted developer and that is very, how do you say,
[Flo]: It will oxidize somehow, but it will still function, which it doesn't work with a lot of other developers.
[Flo]: Use them and then two weeks later they're already gone.
[Flo]: So I'm someone who works often in projects, so one project is
[Flo]: photography and then there's maybe six months absolutely no development at all and stuff still works so that's that was important to give this now how you can reduce and then everything is in a box 20 by 30 centimeters so the whole lab and I just wanted to share this because I figure it out really hard here I can save something this I can make simpler this is a chemistry that really works and that's something I wanted to share
[Kaspar]: Thank you so much and also thank you for sharing this with the listeners in Collaboradio.
[Kaspar]: Clap to COLAB.
[Flo]: Thank you so much.
[Music playing]: Music playing
[Music playing]: Yeah.
[Alwin]: Yeah, nice.
[Kaspar]: Yeah, it goes.
[Kaspar]: Hi, I'm Casper König, and I'm talking now about Labrador Radio, a free radio in Berlin, in Brandenburg, and I would like to make a little report about this homemade festival in Switzerland, in Berghaus.
[Alwin]: Gerlen.
[Alwin]: Good morning, hi Kasper.
[Alwin]: I'm Alvin Weber from Dresden.
[Alwin]: I've been circling circles for a long time.
[Alwin]: I'm a circuit bending enthusiast.
[Alwin]: I'm looking for new keyboards and building new houses.
[Alwin]: What's going through my head?
[Alwin]: I'm sitting here in Switzerland, somewhere on a terrace.
[Alwin]: I have to imagine this for the listeners.
[Alwin]: We're sitting on a terrace opposite a mountain with a bent chair.
[Alwin]: Millions of years of old material.
[Alwin]: There are cows around here that clock people.
[Alwin]: And here are about 60 to 70 people who make a lot of regular stuff.
[Alwin]: And at Homemade I think of family exchange, gang, art, so equality.
[Alwin]: I was in Switzerland for the first time in 2010 at this Homemade research week.
[Alwin]: You have to imagine that.
[Alwin]: A lot of people come together, artists, programmers, musicians, all kinds of things, volunteers, and live together for ten days, cook together, work together, exchange ideas, celebrate together.
[Alwin]: There are a lot of crazy things going on.
[Alwin]: I drove 1200km alone with a car.
[Alwin]: My parents gave me a ride to meet the same freaks and nerds.
[Alwin]: I arrived at the venue the next morning.
[Alwin]: There was Paradise on.
[Alwin]: Nice people.
[Alwin]: A lot of knowledge in the air, a lot of creativity in the air.
[Alwin]: And it was just a life-changing scenario.
[Alwin]: After the week I went back to Dresden and started the Circuit Control Spectacle in Dresden in 2011.
[Alwin]: Because I was really impressed by this week's principle.
[Alwin]: It was just very inspiring.
[Alwin]: And when I think of a homemade, I think of an absolute, bold superpower.
[Alwin]: superpowers like Team Schreger-Superhelden, which can handle a lot of awesome stuff, like biohacking, cooking, soldering, etc.
[Alwin]: A lot of modern tools, lasers, modeling tools, synthesizers.
[Alwin]: P.R.s, visuals, optics, acoustic instruments, socializing, not just crazy.
[Alwin]: I just think of the most positive things I've ever experienced when I'm at home.
[Kaspar]: That's very nice.
[Kaspar]: I'm not very happy about that.
[Kaspar]: Yesterday you said something about it.
[Kaspar]: You thought it could be so utopian.
[Kaspar]: Or you chose a profession.
[Alwin]: Yes, the simulation of utopia.
[Alwin]: It corresponds to a small simulation of utopia.
[Alwin]: The contribution of the environment is like the model of an iron plate.
[Alwin]: It's a beautiful surrounding.
[Alwin]: And if there are still many nice people with nice ideas and ideas and nice contributions and the common sense that equality and equality come together, because everyone has something to offer, everyone wants to know something, everyone is curious, everything is still like big children and they want to bring their projects with them and everyone is looking forward to showing them.
[Alwin]: It's cooked together.
[Alwin]: that there are different processes going on.
[Alwin]: It is the simulation of the utopia, how it could be so beautiful in this direction.
[Alwin]: Of course, the reality is in the simulation of the mountain hut in the Girlen mountain house.
[Alwin]: It is a short beam out of the world of 1200 meters high in such a small bubble, but the structures themselves work in this bubble.
[Alwin]: We exchange a lot of utopian, crazy ideas and things and the knowledge and the power that is here in the R and the creativity are also high.
[Alwin]: specific people from software areas, engineers, art areas, social areas.
[Alwin]: It's just an average bunch of superpowers.
[Alwin]: And that also makes a little utopia.
[Alwin]: You need a gang that works and you need people who want it.
[Alwin]: And people who lead it and want it on stage.
[Alwin]: And in the end you just do your things, work together, eat together and have fun together.
[Alwin]: And that's very, very nice.
[Alwin]: Yeah.
[Music playing]: Thank you.
[Music playing]: Music playing
[Alwin]: What did you grow?
[Alwin]: It was a good question.
[Alwin]: I mean, I grew up with the first, most obvious view.
[Alwin]: A lot of detailed ideas, people bring projects with them.
[Alwin]: You see things that you can't even imagine.
[Alwin]: If someone makes latex or silicone skin with original body hair,
[Alwin]: motor parts, and abstract constructs are produced.
[Alwin]: The growing first line of ideas of people who bring their projects with them and then show them to each other.
[Alwin]: And you are automatically inspired by the ideas yourself.
[Alwin]: So, first of all, growing ideas.
[Alwin]: And of course, it also grows together.
[Alwin]: Or with ideas, it also grows
[Alwin]: problems, you have to find solutions and that is in the technical level or in the engineering level or construction level, of course exactly the same as in a get together with many people.
[Alwin]: Everyone knows how it is in groups, communities, housing communities, families, associations, small groups, large groups.
[Alwin]: There will always be problems.
[Alwin]: The focus is to focus on solutions and not on problems.
[Alwin]: It's a make-up scene, whatever.
[Alwin]: It's always about solutions and not about problems.
[Alwin]: Problems arise and they are always there and will always come and come to us.
[Alwin]: But the energy in the air and the possibilities, it's just hard inspiring that there is always a solution.
[Alwin]: This is hard work, and it has shaped me somehow since 2010, and without the SKMK, the Swiss company for mechatronic art, I would have been sent on this film, and it has so much to do with me.
[Alwin]: I've been able to give workshops for 14 years and travel around the world with people, whether it's only in India, Switzerland, Mexico or Germany.
[Alwin]: At the end of the day, people share things, you exchange ideas, and it's a good time.
[Alwin]: In the end, it's all about solutions and structures.
[Alwin]: We always have 50 people, we need more tables.
[Alwin]: It's a simple problem, it still has to be solved.
[Alwin]: There are difficult and complicated problems, but it's always about solutions and they're out there.
[Alwin]: But only through networking and TeamGyste and Community.
[Kaspar]: Yeah, man, very well said.
[Kaspar]: So good.
[Kaspar]: Do you want to say something on the website where people can find you?
[Alwin]: Yes, the website is very unpretentious, but so circuitcircle.de, so circuit again Schaltkreis Englisch and the Schaltkreis round near Alvin Weber.de is and otherwise Störnfried Bandcamp and Metacnoden, our green tracks, the network behind for the Dresdenapart and circuit control with off-recht halt.
[Alwin]: Thank you so much for the interview, it was fun.
[Alwin]: Have fun with the show, ciao!
[Music playing]: You know, it was a big crowd for all of us.
[Music playing]: Yeah.
[Kaspar]: This was my collab clip.
[Kaspar]: Perfect, yes.
[Kaspar]: I'm making a applause in the end.
[Kaspar]: So when I get the single claps, then I will edit them to a bigger applause.
[Olsen]: Nice.
[Kaspar]: But that's a joke I figured out after finding a title for the program.
[Kaspar]: And now I'm really curious, could you describe what you're doing and for the listeners to understand what they see if they would sit in my position?
[Olsen]: I just mentioned to her I have a strong deterministic system based on a tailpipe that I wrote a script.
[Olsen]: It's an image of a tailpipe from a tuning car.
[Olsen]: And the script gives me a pixel art.
[Olsen]: So it makes each pixel of the image into a color that I then do with a cross stitching yarn, I think, gun, yarn.
[Olsen]: And I reproduce it.
[Olsen]: So it's a pixel art thing.
[Kaspar]: Beautiful.
[Kaspar]: And this is not your first one.
[Olsen]: No, this is my fourth, so it's going to be a cushion.
[Olsen]: And I'm going to make seven, because seven is the infinite number apparently in many religious beliefs.
[Olsen]: It's about the car as a religious object.
[Kaspar]: Yeah, especially Germany.
[Olsen]: Not only.
[Olsen]: I think in Switzerland it's also quite popular.
[Olsen]: If you go to downtown Zurich on a Saturday night, you see them driving around.
[Olsen]: Many of them use tailpipes and many other things.
[Olsen]: So it's all about worshipping a technological object.
[Kaspar]: I'm tuning the sound.
[Olsen]: Tuning the sound, yes.
[Olsen]: And here there's no sound, so it's a still living.
[Kaspar]: Yeah.
[Olsen]: So I kind of... It's up to the person who will sleep on it.
[Olsen]: Maybe they hear the sound on the cushion, or if they just watch it.
[Kaspar]: Yeah.
[Olsen]: So this is something to be found out.
[Kaspar]: Yeah, imaginary sounds are the best.
[Kaspar]: Ghost sound.
[Olsen]: Acosmetics, apparently.
[Kaspar]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Kaspar]: Thank you so much for your explanation.
[Kaspar]: What's your name?
[Olsen]: Olsen.
[Kaspar]: Olsen.
[Kaspar]: Okay, that's in the radio.
[Olsen]: Thank you so much.
[Kaspar]: Thank you.
[Oli]: Hi, I'm Olli Jaggi.
[Oli]: I'm part of the organizing team from Homemade and personally I'm interested in electronic music that's kind of the field I'm working on and also this year I built some sound devices that was very nice to do at workshops that other people held.
[Kaspar]: And you give a workshop to yourself?
[Kaspar]: Sometimes?
[Oli]: Yes, sometimes I do that.
[Oli]: Recently I was in Radeona in Sagreb.
[Oli]: I did a workshop there.
[Oli]: Also I did a crossfade circuit, a small one, so for people to connect their audio stuff and then mix it together.
[Kaspar]: And how did you start being so engaged with homemade?
[Kaspar]: What is the moment that happened to you?
[Oli]: That's a good question.
[Oli]: I actually started with SGMK by attending a workshop.
[Oli]: And it was kind of funny, it was called Experimental Audio Electronics and immediately after that we built like a performance group, the so-called DIY Kamikaze Orchestra, like the people from the workshop did kind of
[Oli]: performance group where we live soldered audio circuits and did this as a performance so people could watch as we soldered and it started to sound at some point that was very nice and through this I kind of got into the community and then I also went to homemade and some years later suddenly I was organizing homemade.
[Kaspar]: And can you tell us the origin of homemade?
[Oli]: Yeah, actually the first, I think, two or three homemates were organized by microkulturprozent.
[Oli]: It was an initiative, I think mainly also from Dominik Landwehr.
[Oli]: And I think after some years they did it, they didn't want to continue, so SGMK took it over and from then SGMK is organizing it like each year.
[Oli]: And this year is the 21st edition.
[Oli]: Exactly.
[Kaspar]: Super.
[Kaspar]: Thank you.
[Kaspar]: Well, I hope there's going to be many, many more because I also think it's still very inspiring every year.
[Kaspar]: There's new things to discover.
[Oli]: Yeah, always new people who join.
[Oli]: That's great.
[Kaspar]: Exactly.
[Kaspar]: And kids, a lot of kids this year.
[Kaspar]: Amazing dynamics.
[Kaspar]: yeah so thank you so much yeah hot weather yeah tonight shower probably yeah the storm a little bit of rain but that's fine yeah after these hot days superb thank you thank you
[Taras]: So my name is Taras.
[Taras]: I'm coming from Ukraine.
[Taras]: I live in Germany for many years now and got interested into playing first just acoustic guitar.
[Taras]: I was playing acoustic guitar for many years and then my
[Taras]: My interest shifted towards more harmonics, overtones and usual techniques of playing guitar, like tuning guitar to resonate on all the same strings.
[Taras]: And then I get deeper into drone music.
[Taras]: that was around like 16 years ago and I started to record with guitar and then without guitar then using field recordings as well and some unusual objects so that my interest into small sound like a micro sound started so for with jigsaw for example I was with bow made some nice recording then I noticed there's like a when you go closer it opens quite another domain
[Taras]: and yeah and then like after coming to Germany I kind of stopped making music but I got interested into abstract photography, into found art, into textures so like street macro that I call it and that also had my interest into videos as well making abstract videos with some homemade setups with scanners, lasers, glass and that stuff that brought me into
[Taras]: kind of these devices, you call it, for very accurate control in your setup.
[Taras]: So when I came back to music I basically used a lot of my photography background in a way how I also set it up.
[Taras]: So I used photography, videography, sliders and to basically study this special effect of sound.
[Taras]: So that and I started really like from not from the scratch but again with the basics
[Music playing]: . .
[Taras]: I added this rubber band instrument, how I call it, just came from my very simple windstick instrument, which I put on this vibration generator, which I used before for semantics, again for visuals.
[Taras]: So this line between visuals and sound for me is very kind of thin.
[Taras]: And then, starting with that, I got
[Taras]: much deeper now into this special sound.
[Taras]: It's called a special field of sound.
[Taras]: It's just like seeing this object, not just something which is one, but it's multi-dimensional.
[Taras]: And you can study this.
[Taras]: I made many, many hours with one stream basically.
[Taras]: And it's also like there's a big part of this, I would say it's the precision, but this precision is not to control, but just to study deeper.
[Kaspar]: And then as a matter of fact, I will explain a little bit what the people could see.
[Kaspar]: So we have a set up with two strings, there's some ebos, there's some regulator to make a really very tiny adaptions to the height of the ebos.
[Kaspar]: Then there's some splash, they call them splash, right back in, or right here, something like that, with microphones almost attached to it.
[Kaspar]: So you play basically the string sound into this splash and then you record it back into the system and you give it another spin through the elastics or through the other.
[Taras]: It can be like
[Taras]: you can combine it, but also you can play it separate.
[Taras]: So usually I mostly play separate and just like tune in to find these resonances between them.
[Taras]: And also like I'm really into like close mic'ing technique, but you would call it ultra-close mic'ing or touch mic'ing.
[Taras]: So like it just, yeah, I often using microphone as a resonator as well.
[Taras]: So it's a part of the instrument basically.
[Kaspar]: Beautiful, beautiful.
[Taras]: And this drumming, for example, that is going on now, I use microphones to play on the drum and record the sound at the same time.
[Kaspar]: Yeah, beautiful, beautiful.
[Kaspar]: So what would you say does homemade mean to you?
[Taras]: It's amazing.
[Taras]: It's a life-changing event, like already.
[Taras]: And I told that on the first day, basically.
[Kaspar]: And you're the first time here, right?
[Taras]: And I'm the first time here.
[Taras]: I was clear on the first day that I found an amazing community of people.
[Kaspar]: Thank you so much for your time.
[Taras]: You're welcome.
[Kaspar]: And then you have a visit to Mulaboradio Berlin.
[Kaspar]: A few names.
[Music playing]: How can you record something so heavy?
[Kaspar]: You are listening to Clap to COLAB, part three.
[Kaspar]: This was a documentation on the homemade festival in Gierlin, Zangalen in Switzerland, which was organized by the Swiss Megatronic Society for Art.
[Kaspar]: I hope you will join us in one month again.